[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these is among the Top Ten Inventions of 2005 according to the US Army?", "correct_answer": "Fido Explosives Detector", "incorrect_answers": ["Achilles Anti-Aircraft Missile", "The G.A.D.G.E.T. Deployable armored personnel vehicle", "The R.E.X. anti-spyware computer software"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ataxiophobia means fear of riding a taxi.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the title of the Johnny Cash song, which tells the story of a man who wants to take revenge on his father for giving him a girls name: A Boy Named.....", "correct_answer": "Sue", "incorrect_answers": ["Amy", "Liz", "May"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous movie director co-produced the 2009 science fiction movie Transformers: Revenge of the Fallen?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["George Lucas", "James Cameron", "Tim Burton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Consuming too much alcohol can raise fats in the blood.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to the frames used to make animated movies?", "correct_answer": "cels", "incorrect_answers": ["frazinoids", "tabloids", "Thraumas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Luke Skywalker in Star Wars: Episode 4?", "correct_answer": "Mark Hamill", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Bacon", "Ewan McGregor", "Samuel L Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The code of Shinsengumi comprised five rules. What was the punishment for breaking these rules?", "correct_answer": "Sepuku", "incorrect_answers": ["Cutting of one finger", "Exile", "Paying six gold coins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie directed by Alfred Hitchcock tells the story of an actress who has been wrongly accused of the murder of her colleague?", "correct_answer": "Murder!", "incorrect_answers": ["The Skin Game", "Sabotage", "Stage Fright"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It was the Internets progenitor and the first large geographically separated network.", "correct_answer": "ARPANET", "incorrect_answers": ["NSFNET", "UUCP", "CSNET"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which independent country was not a Soviet republic?", "correct_answer": "Albania", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia", "Armenia", "Lithuania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city does the action in the film The Conversation occur?", "correct_answer": "San Francisco", "incorrect_answers": ["New York City", "Chicago", "Los Angeles"]}]